<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Links on RAC&#39;s notepad</title>
    <link>//rac.su/categories/links/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Links on RAC&#39;s notepad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 00:45:10 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//rac.su/categories/links/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheap China shopping help</title>
      <link>//rac.su/links/chinashopping/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2017 00:45:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//rac.su/links/chinashopping/</guid>
      <description>Aliexpress Chrome extension If you are using chrome, there is a nice extension available on the chrome store that displays you information about the seller (looking up other products and ratings from him) and especially useful it displays other products it finds with prices and price history chart. The history part looks like its generated by the users of the extension and saving the data to a specific listing whenever a user navigates to it, hence you don&amp;rsquo;t have all data but if you regularly go to a certain product and want to see changes without having to note them down, this is handy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friendly links</title>
      <link>//rac.su/links/friendly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 22:11:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//rac.su/links/friendly/</guid>
      <description> Schools  Lernort Moosbachhof (Switzerland, Zug) Robinson Schule (Switzerland, Hirzel)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GO</title>
      <link>//rac.su/links/go/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 21:24:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//rac.su/links/go/</guid>
      <description> Libraries  CLI with COBRA  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STM32</title>
      <link>//rac.su/links/stm32/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 02:50:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//rac.su/links/stm32/</guid>
      <description> IDE  OpenSTM32 - Workbench  Various  Arduino on STM32 Program STM32F103C8T6 with UART Video STM32 with Arduino on OSX  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNC builds</title>
      <link>//rac.su/links/cnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 02:48:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//rac.su/links/cnc/</guid>
      <description> How to make mini CNC 2D plotter using scrap DVD drive, l293d motor shield &amp;amp; Arduino Interesting CNC build from Techno MTM Snap Simple CNC router DIY CNC for less of 160€ with Arduino 3 Axis Arduino Based CNC Controller Arduino CNC Piccolo - The tiny CNC-bot  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Printing maybe things</title>
      <link>//rac.su/links/3d-printing-maybe-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 02:02:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//rac.su/links/3d-printing-maybe-things/</guid>
      <description> Brio    brio mini: crane   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>360° Video processing</title>
      <link>//rac.su/links/360video/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 01:51:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//rac.su/links/360video/</guid>
      <description> Transform360 Library - Transform from equirectangular to cubemap projection  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ComputerVision</title>
      <link>//rac.su/links/computervision/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 01:48:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//rac.su/links/computervision/</guid>
      <description> Java libraries  BoofCV  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arduino</title>
      <link>//rac.su/links/arduino/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 01:30:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//rac.su/links/arduino/</guid>
      <description> Inventory tracking  Docker image for partkeepr  RFID  Mifare MFRC522 13.56MHz  Input  Capacitive sensing Basic Electronics - Electric charge detector  Speech recognition  uSpeech - Speech recognition toolkit for the arduino Voice Recognition with Arduino  Audio Speech synthesis  TTS Arduino library Talkie - Speech library for Arduino  Power  Basic Electronics - High efficiency regulated Joule thief  MOSFETS  High-Power control with N-Channel MOSFET Using MOSFETS with TTL levels  LED Strips  Wemos led strip Arduino sketch example ESP8266 RGB Strip control Thread about reducing PWM noise RGB Led Strip controlled by an Arduino Adafruit - using RGB led strips RGB LED crossfade BigClive - Build a better RGB LED controller Dimming a 12V LED strip with a mosfet and PWM A WiFi-enabled RGB LED strip controller  Lora  ESP8266 WeMos Shield for HopeRF RFM95 RFM96 RFM98 Lora Modules  Project Cases  ALTINKAYA cheap enclosures and battery holders from Turkey  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>//rac.su/links/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 23:47:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//rac.su/links/hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some links I collected with information about how to use Hugo. Articles about &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;hugo&lt;/a&gt; on this site can be found under the &lt;a href=&#34;//rac.su/tags/hugo&#34;&gt;hugo tag&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>